woolworths.co.uk 2006-12-10

# Woolworths.co.uk

#### Who we are

The woolworths.co.uk website (the 'Website') is owned and operated by Woolworths Plc ('we/us'), a company within Woolworths Group plc.

We are committed to providing users with an Internet experience, which respects their privacy. We adhere to the requirements of the UK Data Protection Act 1998.

We have an up-to-date Data Protection Register entry. This entry can be viewed via [http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk](http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk/).

#### About this Statement - Your Consent

The purpose of this statement is to explain to you how we may use your personal information. By registering as a user of the services provided by Woolworths (whether to order goods or services or otherwise) and by using the Woolworths Website at www.woolworths.co.uk generally you agree to this use.

#### Information you provide and how we use it

##### Personal Details

We require personal details such as your name, address, e-mail, credit card, product and order details so that we can process your order and administer your account (including taking steps to prevent fraud).

##### Information about your use of the Website

In order that we can monitor and improve your shopping experience, we use Coremetrics to gather certain information about how you browse and search and buy from the site, when you use the site, including details of your domain name and IP address, operating system, browser, version, cookie details (see below) and the website that you visited prior to our site. 

To do this we place cookies on your computer that collect information on our behalf, we use this information to constantly improve our services and your shopping experience. Passwords and credit card information are not collected by the Coremetrics system. 

Coremetrics is used to analyse the data collected this is then passed back to us via a secure connection. Our contract with Coremetrics prohibits them from using the data themselves. 

You can opt out from having your data collected by visiting this page

##### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to allow us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements, to determine how frequently particular pages are visited and determine the most popular areas of our Website, and carry out market research.

We also use cookies to personalise your visit to our Website and make it more user-friendly, for example by allowing us to save your password so that you do not have to re-enter it every time.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, though you do not have to. The 'help' portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

Please remember that by disabling cookies you may not be able to place an order on this Website.

For more information about cookies and your rights, please refer to: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

##### Our Products and Services

If you check the relevant box under 'options' on your Account Registration page, we will also use your details to keep you up to date with information on the products, services and special offers offered by Woolworths plc, Streets Online Limited and other companies in the Group, [and to administer contests, competitions and a news e-mail service.]

If, after you have registered, you do not want to receive marketing information from Woolworths plc or Streets Online Limited or any other Group company, then you can unsubscribe at any time by either:

  1. contacting us directly via the unsubscribe facility included in communications that may be sent to you; or 
  2. changing your options in Your Account details. 

##### Digital Services

Where you have ordered Digital Services, we reserve the right to remotely access your computer in order to assess whether Digital Service content and licences have been successfully delivered. We may also request a test/file or other content in order to undertake this exercise. If we do require a test/file, we will contact you with further details nearer the time.

#### Who do we pass personal information to?

##### Third Parties

Unless it is necessary to fulfil your order (including for the delivery of goods and services you have ordered by third parties), we will not provide your personal information (i.e. information you supply that identifies you) to any third party without your consent, or unless we are required to do so by law.

Ways in which we might use your information to fulfil your order may include passing it on to employees and agents of the Group to administer any accounts, products and services and passing it on to a technical partner to carry out processing of your personal information on our behalf.

If you check the relevant box under 'options' on your Account Registration page, we will also provide your information to other carefully selected third parties so that they can send you details of their products, offers and services that may be of interest to you. We will not pass your personal data unless you have consented to this use. If you no longer wish to receive such information, you can change your options in your Account details at any time.

We may also provide some general statistical information about the user base, sales patterns, traffic volumes and related matters may be passed on to reputable third parties. However, these details will not include information personally identifying the individual user.

##### Data Security

We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. All the data collected by us is stored on a secure server. The secure server software encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us.

##### Information we receive from third parties

We may supplement the information that you provide to us with information that we receive from third parties, for example, collected from other members of your household.

##### Access to your Information

You may access and update all of your data via: <https://www.woolworths.co.uk/ww_p2/account/index.jhtml?redirect=account_home> or by updating your details in Your Account.

##### Other Links

Please be aware that our site may link to other web sites which may be accessed through our site. We are not responsible for the data policies, content or security of these linked web sites.

#### Our Terms

Please note that all products and services are supplied subject to our Terms & Conditions of Sale.

#### Contact Us

If you have any comments or queries in connection with our privacy policy, please contact our Customer Services team.

Return to the Customer Services Home Page.
